good afternoon hello hello
добрый день здравствуйте здрасте вот
two blogs met me I'm from ukraine
встретились два блога меня я из украины
often your
мне часто ваши
fans write it to me if you're here and we
поклонники пишешь его если ты здесь и
'll talk with glory and here
славой поговорим а тут и с какими-то
it will be difficult for you
непонятными со мной сложно будет вам
to talk to me with some incomprehensible maybe yes I'm talking about the
поговорить возможно да я общаюсь на тему
war and Russia is interested you see  you
войны и россию интересует вот видите вы
already started with the fact that you don’t know what
уже начали с того что вы не знаете о чем
you are talking about that’s what we can talk about not
говорите вот о чем мы можем говорить не
I’m asking you I’m asking about this topic in
я вас спрашиваю я вот на эту тему в эзра
ezra miller she just asks me a
миллер она спрашивать просто у меня к
question for you if you don’t know what’s
вам вопрос если вы не знает что
going on why are you even starting a
происходит зачем вы вообще начинаете
stupid question  than we want your
глупый вопрос чем нами я хочу ваше
attitude
отношение
towards me, I’m not at all interested in
ко мне вообще неинтересно вас
commenting on you, I’ll tell you more, so
комментировать я вам скажу больше то
far the question itself has been
пока что самый вопрос неправильно
put incorrectly, that is, you are not an interesting
поставил то есть вы вас не интересную
topic of the war, Russia and there are not 5 but not
тему войны россию и там не 5 а не
interested in the war that is in your heads
интересует война который у вас в головах
and then the war that you  they announced Russia
а потом война который вы объявили россии
which Russia showed before but at the same time you
который проявили россии до но при этом
don’t understand what you are and what topics you
не понимаете что вы ее а какие темы вас
are interested in
интересуют
what topics I am interested in such
какие меня тем интересны такие темы еще
topics I tell you again, so I called you with  howling pull
раз говорю вот я вам назвал свою тянуть
first name yours let's
первые назовите свои давайте о семейных
talk about family values now it's not a prior
ценностях поговорим о это сейчас не в
ty they talking on March 7 you don't
приоритете они общаясь на 7 марта вам
need this because now there is a war in ou
такого и не надо потому что сейчас война
country when you came here in vain you a
в нашей стране когда вы зря сюда вышли
e not ready for why you came out you are viola
вы не готовы к почему вы вышли вы
ed in your  in your head the war is
нарушенным у вас в голове война у вас
not even in the country inside the species, that
война даже не в стране внутри вида то
is, you don’t want you a special operation, no matter
есть вы не хочу вас спецоперация неважно
what it’s called, so there is your
как она называется так вот есть ваша
country attacked my country attacked the
страна напала на мою страну напала на
pallas took a run otherwise don’t
паллада совершила разбег иначе не
confuse anything don’t confuse wait
путайте ничего не путаем подождите вы
you declared war on us 8 years we  shouted
нам объявили войну 8 лет мы кричали
wait 8 years you attracted
подождите 8 лет вы привлекали
public opinion said
общественное мнение говорили
accumulated that you are at war with Russia
аккумулировали что вы воюете с россией
we absolutely do not need such a salute and
не такой салют нами надо абсолютно и
after that it suddenly turned out that after
после этого вдруг оказалось что через
eight years we were only on your coat
восемь лет мы на вас только на пальто
with us throw out seven years after eight
с нами вываливай семь лет через восемь
years you attacked 8 years ago on the fourteenth
лет вы напали 8 лет назад четырнадцатом
year and now a more full-scale
году а сейчас более полномасштабное
invasion
вторжение
why
почему
because I will tell you guys I fought
потому что я вам скажу ребятки я воевали
by myself let me tell you
сами собой давайте я скажу
won you fought  with yourself here you
выиграли вы воевали сами с собой вот вы
settled down on both channels you do with
устроились обоих канале you do со
all sorts of Nazi battalions many
всякими батальонами нацистскими многими
other things burning miles ideas in the house of
другими вещами сжигания миль идеи в доме
trade unions and so on and so on I
профсоюзов и так далее и так далее у
have a question for you really when you come
меня вопрос к вы правда когда сюда
out here you ask stupid questions you don’t
выходите задаете глупые вопросы не
understand why you yourself brought your country
понимаете для чего вы сами свою страну
and what Russia is saving you from today,
довели и от чего сегодня вас спасает
we talk a lot about but without
россия мы очень много говорить о но без
facts, tell me the day and
фактов назовите мне день и
date when the bacchanalia began
дату когда началась вакханалия
guys fact 1 guys that you are
ребятки факт 1 ребятки что вы
your country before what is happening with you,
свою страну до того что у вас происходит
look you don’t want to answer
смотрите вы не хотите отвечать на
questions I’m not going to answer
вопросы я вообще не собираюсь отвечать
at all  what is here and because you are being clever,
на что тут и потому что сидишь умничаешь
I tell you again you came here not to
я тебе еще раз говорю ты сюда вышел не
prepare look let’s say they are
подготовиться посмотрите допустим они
prepared for the coins of the gang you and you
подготовлены для монет банда ты а вы не
can’t my problem is that
можете моя проблема что
on February 26, 2011 the Russian
26 февраля 2011 года российская
Federation troops of the Russian Federation
федерация войска российской федерации
captured the Parliament of Crimea from that
захватили парламент крыма с этого
moment the beginning of
момента начала
Ukraine we  created this position you
украины мы создали эту позицию вы
declared war on russia you are now sitting and
объявили войну россии вы сейчас сидите и
demanding all the victims of the steed you are screaming  that
требуйте все жертвы стида вы кричите что
you are not guilty of
вы ни в чем не виноваты эти больше хочу
anything, I want to say more, I think that it is necessary to bring the whole of
сказать я считаю что нужно привлечь всю
Ukraine to collective responsibility, you are
украину коллективной ответственности вы
all to blame,
все виноваты
they wanted a
они хотели
world
мирового
organization for generating a completely
организация генерации совсем другой
different genocide was carried out in the Donbass when the
проводился геноцид на на донбассе когда
protégé is responsible for his words these for his
протеже ответе за свои слова эти за свои
words throughout his tell me what
слова на протяжении своей скажите какова
to understand
понимать
what day the war began in the Donbass, they
какого дня началась война на донбассе
cried and started shouting that you absolutely got a
заплакали и начали кричать что вас
line
абсолютно линейки
, tell me what I ask you
получается рассказывайте что я вас прошу
and
и
add up everyone who
сложите все кто
sits and justifies when they started
сидит и оправдывает когда начались были
eating it before him, the action frame in the
есть она до него действо кадре на
Donbass took place now choose everyone
донбассе происходили вот выбрать всех
tell me when they started
скажите мне когда начались вот
tell me  when the murders began
расскажите мне когда начались убийства
in the Donbass, who are you talking to baths
на донбассе вы с кем разговаривать ванны
tell me what is it like now in the Donbass with
скажите какова какова сейчас донбассе с
you who they talked to you to
вами с кем там разговаривали с вами
talk to tell me when in the background you were talking to
разговаривать скажите когда на фоне со
me imperceptibly you can’t listen
мной разговаривал незаметно не слушать
you can’t tell the date
не умеете вы не можете назвать дату
when you are watching we have been talking to you for
когда вы смотрите мы говорим с вами уже
five  minutes
пять минут
special answer the question  to
специальными отвечайте на вопрос
answer
отвечать
if you are a propagandist usually not a
если вы же пропагандиста обычно не
propagandist I am Ukraine
пропагандист я украина
when to judge and
когда судить и
judge and judge for that yes I condemn the
судить и судить для того да я осуждаю
killing of people in the Donbass because
убийство людей на донбассе потому что
Russia came to Ukraine at the beginning
россия пришла в украину в начале
I understood you correctly Russia means
я правильно вас понял россия значит
doing everything correctly not Russia
правильно все делать не россии
began the
начала
Ukrainian year the
украинском году
murder of Ukrainians  a lot more no
убийство украинцев много больше нет
no call me
ни чтобы это назовите мне
search
поискать
turned off turned off the sound what other
отключил отключил звук какие у тебя ещё
questions do you all listen to me no I
вопросы все послушайте меня нет я тебя
don’t listen to you at all, that is, you can’t
вообще не слушать то есть вы не можете
name
назвать
if you if I’m not interested in why the
если вы если я вам не интересны почему
same thing says and now you’ll see
же самое говорит и сейчас увидите почему
why if growth  I show that you are a stupid
вот если рост показываю что ты глупый
person, let me see these as not when the
человек пусть меня эти как не когда
first feeling in the Donbass was, I
первое чувство на донбассе было я тебе
answered you, but then there was a murder in the
ответил но тогда было убийство на
Donbass, and I will say on April 12, 2014
донбассе а я скажу 12-го апреля 2014
, the Russian institute captured the city of
года российский институт захватил город
Slavyansk and from that time the
славянск и с этого времени началась
war began in the Donbass, they began to kill
война на донбассе начали убивать у
borders knows up to this point
границы знает до этого момента
our alliance of fighting was not
нашего союза боевых действий не был
if you are not just propaganda on you
если вы не просто пропаганда на вас
paris you s  azhima for tell me what
париж вы зажима за скажите какие
murders were all
убийства были все
you understand
вы понимаете
yes so you will lose because
да так вы проиграете потому что
tell me
скажите
when the war began in the donbass
когда началась война на донбассе у
everyone who shouted there in the comments you
всех кто там кричал в коментари
will fall for uncle glory he will roll you there according to the
попадешься на дядю славу он тебя там по
facts roll out I fell for uncle
фактам раскатайте я попался на дядю
glory and that uncle glory I rolled
славу и что дядя слава меня раскатал
me  not a word can answer a single
я ни слова не может ответить ни на один
factual question, so in fact he
фактический вопрос так по факту он
starts an abstract saying, they said not
начинает абстрактный говорим говорили не
so global now turned off and to those
такое global сейчас отключился и тем кто
who are on his stream, but something hangs
у него на стриме а что-то там вешает
noodles there, so what kind of intellectually
лапшу так каким же интеллектуально
educated individuals, that is, this
образованным личностям так то есть этот
former convict before  who was sitting in the zone
бывший зэк до который сидел на зоне
now, he’s
сейчас его
in chat roulette, it’s just there about some kind of
в чат-рулетке просто там про какой-то в
toltaq in this and a sound, and now they
этом и звука толтак а сейчас его
took him for payment like that, but he
взяли на оплату так но он за бабки
propagandizes this topic for grandmas, there’s a hole there
пропагандируют вот эту тему там пробоину
and you’re on, but this
и ты дальше но вот эта
technique is so that’s just
методика такая так то есть просто
bazaar bazaar bazaar bazaar would score about nothing and not one fact not to answer vodka full denied and for balakovo I am Ukrainian about a
балаково я украинскую о
clear before that some other
четкого перед этим еще кое-то
propagandist  distish papoose also merged
пропагандистского papoose тоже слилось
they all of them all they have such a tactic
они все они все у них такая тактика
to translate everything into emotions something tamara
перевести все на эмоции что-то тамара
tells something there without stopping
чего-то там рассказывает без остановки
talking
говорить
instead of asking a specific
вместо того чтобы задать конкретный
question get a specific answer or
вопрос получить конкретный ответ или
get a question give language he can answer not a single
получить вопрос дать язык он ни на один
question therefore  whoever is there in
вопрос может ответить поэтому кто там в
italy will write in a comment
комментарий италия будет писать
if you got uncle glory in short, he
если тебе попался дядя слава короче он
would have unwound you gu look at your
бы тебя размотал гу смотрите на своего
uncle glory so he knows very well that
дядю славу так он прекрасно знает что
he is now to be dipped in the [ __ ] with his face,
его сейчас макнуть мордой в [__]
so if
поэтому же если
you speak you must be responsible for your
ты говоришь ты должен отвечать за свои
words as if you say that  ukraine
слова как если ты говоришь что украина
killed people there in the donbass, let's
убивала там людей на донбассе давай
say when ukraine makes the first
скажем когда украина сделать первое
murder in the donbass, if ukraine was
убийство на донбассе вот если украину
killed by it that some day it began
убивала она что какого-то дня начала
to kill in the donbass and when it was the
убивать на донбасс и когда это было
ninety-first year of
девяносто первом году
2014 if in 2014 then when so if we
2014 если в 2014 то когда так если мы
parse this chronology very clearly
разбираем эту хронологию очень четко
it can be seen that before the Russian
видно что до того как российские
mercenaries de militants, the house with the flexible tower
наемники де боевики дом с башней гибким
did not come with detachments and did not start  and to
так не пришли с отрядами и не за начали
capture Ukrainian cities there
захватывать украинские города никаких
were no dead there were no military operations on the
погибших никаких военных действий на
territory of the Donetsk and Luhansk regions
территории донецкой и луганской области
February 26, 2014 I will specifically
26 февраля 2014 года я специально буду
speak in Russian that all these
говорить по-русски что у нас эти все
fans of Uncle Glory listened to us there
фанаты дяди славы там послушали
Russian troops captured the
российские войска захватили парламент
Crimean parliament, so that is February 26, 2014
крыма так то есть 26 февраля 2014 года
so russia has already made an act of aggression
так россия уже сделала акт агрессии по
against it, we’ll fix it all in
отношению к ней это все зафиксируем
international documents in resolutions
международных документах в резолюциях
why he doesn’t want to because
почему он не хочет потому что против
he won’t be able to say anything against it here is a
этого он ничего не сможет сказать вот
credit for the fact of
кред на факт захвата парламента
the seizure of parliament  for years,
давать война на донбассе у плена 8 лет
it’s like this, and not like that, that the act furnishes
именно так а не этак акта обставляет
something like how Ukraine arrived and started
вроде как украина приехала и начала
bombing the Donbass, the meaning of
бомбить донбасс смысл
what happened, that is, on April 12, 2014
что же было а то есть 12 апреля 2014
, militants from Russia captured the city of
года боевики из россии захватили город
Slavyansk, they started throwing people into the basement,
славянск начали людей кидать на подвал
so they
так
armed the local criminals, they made
вооружили местный криминалитет сделали
the people’s mayor there a criminal one
там народного мэра criminal щека одно
Ponomarev’s cheek  two days later, the
пономарёва через два дня была захвачена
throat was also captured by militants;
также боевиками горловка потешается в
this one without years was also the Russian military
этот без лет был тоже российские военные
in Gorlovka the next day after the
в горловке на следующий день после
capture they killed a deputy of the local council
захвата убили депутата местного совета
Gorlovka residents for a fisherman, that is, here you have the
горловчане на рыбака то есть вот вот вам
first victim of a murder in the Donbas so the
первая жертва убийства на донбассе так
militants killed the deputy these from Russia
убили депутата боевики вот эти из россии
they killed the deputy of the city council that they
они убили депутата городского совета что
removed the Russian flag and raised  a Ukrainian
снял российский флаг и поднял украинский
and another student were killed there, these are all facts,
и еще студента убили оного это все факты
we can say such and such a date there
можем сказать такого то числа у там 17
April 17, before the age of 14 they killed this fisherman they
17 апреля до 14 года убили этого рыбака
took 20 they brought 17 they put these
отвели 20 привели 17 укладывают в этих
days there were
днях был этих никаких до 12-го апреля
no murders in the Donbas until April 12, that
никаких убийств на донбассе не было то
is,
есть
this  through these militants,
сия через своих вот этих боевиков начала
hostilities began, seizures of government bodies and
боевые действия захваты органов власти и
law enforcement agencies and
органов правопорядка и
people who were not supposed to escape from
люди не которые должны были убежать из
these territories, so they killed someone
этих территорий так вот и убили кого-то
in the basement, threw them there, there are nuts, a
на подвал кинули там вот есть гайки
family of
семью
Protestants, so they killed
протестантов так убили
they started killing people, of course, that the
начали убийство людей естественно что
state should protect  these people
государство должно защитить этих людей
because it is necessary if
потому что нужно если бы
I gathered a detachment of fifty rivers to come
я собрал отряд из пятидесяти реки пришел
to seize the department  the police in the city of
захватить отделение полиции в городе там
Bryansk, for example, or there, Dagestan,
брянской например или там дагестане
Makhachkala, so that the Russian authorities would do with me, of
махачкале чтоб со мной сделал российская
course, the rule would be to counter what
власть конечно правило бы контр как у
you call a terrorist
вас называется террористическую операцию
operation and kicked everyone out absolutely the same thing
так и вышибло всех абсолютно тоже самое
did Ukraine announced an
сделала украина объявила
anti-terrorist operation to
анти-террористической операции чтобы
knock out these militants Russia
выбить вот этих боевиков россия
ruled across the Ukrainian border
управляла через украинский границу так
so all these bulls went to clean up
вот таких всех быков пошли к зачистке
these formations, so
эти формирования переправлялись так
all sorts of motorolas were transported, although motorola was still
всякие моторолы хотя motorola еще в
lit up in Kharkov before that, so there
харькове засветился до этого так не
were no minting rallies in Kharkov
чекана были митинги харькове завозили
, Russian titushki were imported, so the Russians
вот титушек российских так российские
climbed in, these are not there and the retiree and,
полезли вот этих там нет и отставник и
so to speak, such vacationers in order
так сказать такие отпускники для того
for Russia  didn’t send them officially
чтобы россия не посылала их официально
according to the documents, so they kind of wrote to
по документам так они как бы писали джо
joe on vacation, so they sent them in well-
в отпуске ду так и их отправляли
coordinated groups completely here
слаженными группами полностью сюда
there are all the documents for an international
есть это все документы на международный
document there is a UN
документ есть резолюция оон так у
resolution  for me it is not for
он же это все кричит не для меня не для
me  it screams that these
меня он это кричит чтобы его вот эти
viewers are better because he is paid by the
зрителей лучше потому что ему платят
grandmas of the Russian Federation for
бабки российской федерации за то что он
wrapping these shells here, why,
окутает вот этих ракушек почему потому
because for Russia this is very important and you need to
что для россии это очень важно и надо
show, let's say to your secret clip,
показывать скажем своему тайному клипсу
that they are doing the right thing during the war circle for the
что они правильно делают в войну кружок
first two or three days  somehow people
первых два три дня еще как-то люди
took out there fighting biolaboratories
вывозили там нато боремся биолаборатории
all [ __ ] but 5 months have already passed even
всякая фигня но прошло 5 месяц уже даже
those who doubted already look
те кто сомневался уже смотрю служит
like cocaine is serving as one militarization if
кокаина как один милитаризация если
Ukraine has more and more weapons then
оружие украине все больше и больше тогда
you will be 11 if no one is
ты к одиннадцати фикации если никто не
going and will not be able to capture the thin
собирается и не сможет захватить тонкий
view of everyone  these Natsiks, that is, Ukraine, they
вид всех этих нациков то есть украину не
won’t capture the nickname, they’re already raking them away, left Kharkov,
захватят ника уже там отгребают ушли от
Kiev, left the serpentine one, now a
харькова киева ушли со змеиного сейчас
gesture of goodwill is being prepared near Kherson
готовится жест доброй воли под херсоном
and so on, that is
и так дальше то есть и
, this Russian clip needs to be explained somehow
вот этому клипсу российском надо как-то
and this topic should be pumped over to the dam
и вот эту тему так прокачивать дамбе
or mazda  they killed bamos, this is what
либо mazda убили бамос это то что
clings, but this is for the living voters,
цепляет а вот это избирателях за живого
and yes, if a person does not understand what happened
а да если человек не разбирается что там
there  and they say we went there in blue
происходило на синюю говорят мы туда
because Ukraine bombed Donetsk for 8 years, of
пошли потому что украина 8 лет бомбила
course, a person who doesn’t
донецк конечно человек который не
understand later and gave captivity, they
разбирается он потом и плену дал они
bombed Russia, it seems everything
бомбили россия защищает вроде все
turned out so if this person sees
сложилось так если этот человек видит
an alternative point of view and according to the
альтернативную точку зрения и по датам
dates, he sees that Russia was before
виде что россия до того как российские
these Russian militants  no one entered at all
эти боевики не зашли никто вообще никого
killed no one because no one fought
не убивал потому что никто не воевал
Russian militants began to fight
начали воевать российские боевики
armed they began to seize
вооруженные они начали захватывать
the authorities they began to seize
органы власти они начали захватывать
law enforcement structures so they
правоохранительные структуры так они
began to unload criminals
начали выгружать криминалитет и
and this flow of mercenaries became
вот этот поток наемников стал все больше
more and more until there were some
больше и больше до были некоторые
sympathizers among the local population
сочувствующие среди местного населения
for example, if we take it now to this
например если взять сейчас нам к этот
Dagestan that there will not be among the local
дагестан что не найдется среди местного
population who are ready to dam this
населения которые готовы дамка это
uprising or to seize
восстание или захватить
the police station, of course they will find it, as I
отделение полиции конечно найдет как я
think there are a lot of people who are
думаю там очень много есть людей которые
against Putin, Tallinn, the war against
против путина таллина война против
Russia, but this does not mean that it is necessary to
россии но это же не значит что надо
seize the police station  Department
захватывать отделение полиции отделение
FSB and then that’s why all these propagandists are
фсб и тогда поэтому все эти пропагандист
very pleasant in the evening, this uncle Slava got caught,
очень приятные вечеру попался этот дядя
so before that, something else without knowing
слава так перед этим еще кое-то не зная
nameless propaganda rushes caught, I’ll
безымянная пропаганда мчится попалась ее
also post it separately and write this uncle’s words
тоже отдельно выложу и этого дяди словах
in the comments, so you
напишите в комментариях так что вы
say you took from this dialogue how you
скажем вы взяли из этого диалог как вы
we saw this
увидели вот этого
Russian propagandist because
российского пропагандиста так как
I forgot to evaluate this defensive reaction from him
оценить его вот эту защитную реакцию с
who there are no minutes of
забыла кого нет минут
speaking up the problem instead of
заговаривания проблемы вместо того чтобы
answering specifically on the facts in
отвечать конкретно по фактам по
chronology, write what do you think he is
хронологии напишите как вы думаете он
just such a light cynical
просто вот такой light циничная
individual or is he really so
особь так или он реально настолько
low intellectual that he does not understand
интеллектуальна низкий что не понимает
doesn’t understand these things for some reason,
не понимает вот этих вещей каких то так
or is he a very smart and cunning
или он очень умный и хитрый
person who is working out this
человек который отрабатывает вот эту
agenda, which they have now let down on
повестку на которую сейчас спустили на
these Russian bloggers in the room,
российских вот этих блогеров комнате у
we will have another video up to 2 guys, the
нас будет еще ролик до 2 ребята
schoolchildren admitted that they are paid for
школьники признали что им платят за
extinguishing, they are sitting the bill in the back cage
тушение сидят счет в клетке задка
very interesting so we will continue to
очень интересно так мы продолжим
roll them to smithereens and dunk them in
раскатывать их в пух и прах макать их
cocoa  shki so from it so and our election of the
какашки так из нее же так а наш избрание
strength of ukraine will be their poppy you in our
силы украины будут их мака ты в нашу
glorious ukrainian for the world well
славную украинскую за мир ну
subscribe put like peter i made and the
подписуйтесь ставте лайк петр i made и
comments of the lithuanians kind of
комментариям литовцы вида
flew we mima showed you not to our
слетала мы майма показала ты не нашим
ukrainians and russians and the whole world with
украинцам и россиянам и всему свету с
whom we are on my right  you lived right in Ukraine
кем мы моих справа по украине